Priti Naik

Mulund East, Mumbai-400081

E: pritinaik2410@gmail.com | P: 9321039902

An enthusiastic and high driven professional targeting middle level assignments in News Content Writing and Journalism with a reputed organization.

SUMMARY

Ambitious, independent and curious. My knack for journalism and current affairs is by virtue of my drive and eagerness to excel as a news writer. With 2.6 years of experience as News Content Writer and Sub-Editor, I have furthered by journalism skills through interning, editing, covering current affairs and feature writing.

EXPERIENCE

News Shots U.S. // Content Writer // April 2020 – September 2020 (Part-time)

- Ability to **articulate articles in 60 words** giving better understanding of the news.
- Can cover stories on a wide range of topics like **national/state/entertainment**.
- Writing Long Reads on various current news topics.
- **Ideating and developing content** for knowledge news cards based on history and world affairs.

NewsBharati Mumbai // Sub Editor // December 2017 – February 2020

- Worked on **national news** which largely covered **politics**, **crime and major stories from states**.
- Worked with editors to update existing news stories and to create new reports.
- **Proofread, edited, and evaluated final copy** to verify content aligned with established guidelines.
- **Team player** with the confidence to take the lead and guide other employees when necessary (e.g., with content development, creation, and editing of content)
- Scan various **websites**, **newspapers**, **magazines**, **social media**, **online content** and other sources for latest information on entertainment, news events, current events, etc., in order to collect information for posting on latest news.

Mantralaya Mumbai // Internship // May 2016 – June 2016

- Worked in the Directorate General Information of Public Relations (DGIPR) department of Audiovisual Team.
- Written articles for Mahanews (social website).

Mi Marathi Mumbai // Internship // September 2014 – November 2014

- Worked under the output production team as an Assistant Producer.
- Maintaining Rundown and handling News Bulletin with deciding visual content for Audio Visual clips, Audio Byte, Audio Visual Byte, headlines etc.

SKILLS

- Strong communication and interpersonal skills.
- An eye for detail ensuring stories/ content are fine-tuned and edited maintaining the reporting standards with a creative flair.
- Good understanding of reporting having covered stories working on desk, coordinating with reporters, graphic designer's Editorial skills for publishing in Web media.
- Ability to work well within flexible schedules.

EDUCATION

- Master's in Communication and Journalism // 2017
- Bachelors of Mass Media Specialised in Journalism // 2014

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth : 24th October, 1993

Marital Status : Single

Languages Known: English, Hindi, Marathi, and Malayalam

Hobbies : Reading, Dancing, Music